欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
鳕鱼角 前情提要
Previously on Hightown...
-过来  -你们想干嘛
Come here. - Now what you boys want?
走
Go!
我在考虑欧文·弗劳利
I'm thinking Owen Frawley.
-冉冉升起的毒贩新星  -肖恩·弗劳利的侄子
- Up and coming dealer. - Shane Frawley's nephew.
你做副手 好吧
You take second lead, all right?
你侄子在招惹是非
Nephew's bringing some heat.
你该怎么办就怎么办
You gotta do what you gotta do.
有什么可以帮到你的吗 警官
How can I help you, officer?
-我是来买装备的  -请进吧
I'm here for some gear. Well, come on in.
尿检女士来了
Hey, your pee test lady is here.
你和另一个女孩是周六入住的
You and the other girl checked in Saturday.
-什么女孩  -她什么都记不得了
- What girl? - She can't remember shit.
昏迷两天
It's a two- day blackout.
蕾妮 我的天 你怎么来了
Renee? Oh, my God. What are you doing here?
你能不能给我份工作
Actually, could you give me a job?
我都不敢相信 你终于给我打电话了
I can't believe you finally called me.
很快我会让你帮我做点事情
Soon I'm gonna ask you to do some things for me.
-好吗  -好
Is that okay? - Yeah.
我是莎拉·基根 他们让我找你报到
Hi, I'm Sarah Keegan I was told to report to you.
他们在福尔布鲁克找到了我的车
They found my car in Fall Brook.
你知道这女孩是谁吗
Do you know who the girl is?
我只想知道到底发生了什么
I just need to know what happened.
我想了很多关于你的事
♪'Ithoughtalot ofthings Aboyt you ♪
j Ithought a lot of things About you ♪
我想了很多关于你的事
♪'I thought a lot of things About you ♪
我想了很多关于你昀事
♪ I thought a lot of things About you ♪
我睡不着只想着你
♪ Istayed awake ♪ust thinking about you ♪
♪ I stayed awake ♪ust thinking about you ♪
但现在我离开了
♪ But now I'm away ♪
你必须得留下
♪ You had to stay ♪
明天属于我
♪ Tomorrow's a day of mine ♪
不再有你
♪ That you won't be in ♪
我也想说我只是在享受生活
♪ I tried to say I was just having fun ♪
♪'〔tried to say 〔was just having fun ♪
但我知道你就是对的那个
♪'But Ireally knew That you were the one ♪
♪ But I really knew That you were the one ♪
但我知道你就是对的那个
现在我走了
♪ And now that I'm gone ♪
♪And now that I'm gone ♪
我知道我错了
♪I see I was wrong ♪
♪ I see I was wrong ♪
我早该明白的
♪ Ishould have known AlI along ♪
时间会证明一切
♪ That time would tell ♪
离开你一周时间
♪A week without you ♪
我应该要忘记
♪ I should forget ♪
♪ I should forget ♪'
我应该要忘记
♪ I should forget ♪
离开你两周时间
♪ Two weeks without you ♪
我还在想着你说的话
♪And I'm still thinking about The things that you said ♪
♪And Im still thinking about The things that you said ♪
我还在想着你说的话
♪And I'm still thinking about The things that you said ♪
假期 依然可爱
♪Vacation ♪ust another love- in ♪
♪ Vacation ♪ust another love- in ♪
假期 希望你能爱我
♪Vacation I hope you love me ♪
假期 你能念着我吗
♪ Vacation Would you think of me? ♪
我觉得我要不告而别
♪ I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye ♪
♪I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye ♪
我觉得你知道为什么
♪ I think that you know The reason why ♪
要是我留下呢
♪ What if I was to stay? ♪
事情是否会不一样
♪ Would things turn out Some other. way?
反正我也不会知道了
♪ I'lI never know anyway ♪
像你这么敲门的 不是毒虫就是条子
You know, only junkies and cops knock like that.
瞧瞧你 两项都占了
You know? And lookie here. We got a twofer.
彼得 拜托 开门 我得
Petey, come on. Open up. I gotta- -
老天 这他妈是刺刀吗
Jesus, is that a fucking bayonet?
家传宝物
Family heirloom.
虽然不是我家的
Well, not my family.
别人把这当钱付给我的
Got it as payment.
可他妈值钱了
It's worth a lot of fucking money.
赶紧把那玩意儿收起来 让我进去
Man, put that thing away and let me in.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
来吧 宝贝 来吧
Come on, baby. Come on.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
所以
So. ...
你要什么 老样子吗
what you want, your usual?
不 我不是来嗑的
No, Im not here to score.
你熟这姑娘吗
You know this girl?
熟啊 但显然不如你
Yeah, but not as good as you, obviously.
你俩当时打得那叫一个火热啊
You two looked like you were getting pretty friendly.
我在这儿认识她的吗
I met her here?
老天 女人 对 你在这儿认识她的
Jesus Christ, woman. Yes, you met her here.
然后你俩就走了
And then you two took off.
她是什么人
Who is she?
我要的东西你从来都不给我
Why should I give you what you want
凭什么你要什么我就得给你啊
when you never give me what I want?
拜托 老兄 我这辈子都不可能跟你睡的
Come on, dude. I'm never gonna fuck you.
你到底认不认识她
You know her or not?
好 好得很
Nice. Really nice.
拜托 老兄
Come on, man, um,
我是真的担心她 好吗
I'm actually worried about her, okay?
我觉得可能出事了
I think something might have happened.
行吧 她叫维罗妮卡
Fine. Her name is Veronica.
谢谢你 她姓什么
Thank you. Veronica what?
鬼知道她姓什么 她是个妓女
Veronica who- the- fuck- knows? She's a working girl.
我是在一个跟我有往来的毒贩子那里认识她的
She- - I met her through a dealer that I do business with.
行 她电话号码多少
AlI right, what's her number?
你上网看看 新后台网
Check the net. New Back Page.
她应该就是在那儿卖的
I think that's where she sells her wares.
好 行
Okay. All right.
可以 谢了 我得走了
Cool, thank you. I gotta run.
来都来了 我还是要点东西
Hey, since I'm here, I might as well pick something up
下班用
for after work. -
有两个过去了
There are two coming your way.
嗨 弗兰基 你还好吗
Hi, Frankie. How are you?
现在好多了
Better now.
你带来了吗
Did you bring it?
-带来了  -好
Yeah. - Okay.
我要你伸手到桌子下面
I want you to reach under the table
把东西放在我膝盖上
and place it on my knee.
好
Okay.
好姑娘
Good girl.
怎么了
What is it?
就
It's just
我会不会惹上麻烦啊
could I get in trouble for this?
会 很大的麻烦
Yeah. A lot of trouble.
你介意吗
Is that a problem for you?
因为我从来没做过什么真正的坏事
I've just never really done anything bad.
那你又得到了什么呢
And what has that gotten you?
什么都没有
Nothing.
我和我祖母一起住
I live with my grandmother.
哪儿都没去过
I've never gone anywhere.
我也没有朋友
I- I don't have friends.
没有孩子
I don't have kids.
我
I don't
我什么都没有
I don't have anything.
你有我
Well, you have me.
只要你听我的 我会给你一切
And if you let me, I'll give you everything.
我真的很想要
I want that so bad.
即便这意味着需要你做更多坏事吗
Even if it means more bad things?
要我做什么都可以
I'll do anything.
嗨
Hi.
-嗨  -你在做饭吗
Hi. Oh, you cooking?
这是什么 海市蜃楼吗
What is this, a mirage?
我在给你做早饭
I'm making you breakfast.
因为你最近工作非常努力
Cause you've been working really hard lately
-我很为你骄傲  -得了吧
- and I'm proud of you. Aw, come on.
是真的
It's true.
我知道 我一直磨着你 要你回家
I know Ive been on you about being home,
但这其实不公平
but it's not really fair.
毕竟你是个条子 不是什么银行家
I mean, you're a cop, not a banker.
所以
So.
没事啦
we're good.
你真是太棒了
You are amazing.
我正在办一个很大的案子
You know, I'm working on this, uh, really big case right now.
确实需要一些空间
And I could use the headspace.
行 没问题
Yeah, no problem.
我请我妈来搭把手了 所以
I, uh, asked my mom to help out a little, so...
好主意
Good idea.
这真的太好吃了
This is so good.
那老兄的身子就卡在11号出口牌子里了
Homeboy's body was stuck in the Exit 11 sign.
-不是上头 是里头  -是啊
Not on, in. Yeah.
你很想念这些吗
You miss any of that?
怎么可能
Hell no.
退休是最棒的
Retirement is great.
我想也是
I'll bet.
你就想聊这个吗
Is that what you wanted to talk about?
怎么可能
Hell no.
我就 我带你出来是为了
I just, um- I brought you out so we could, uh,
聊聊 拓展人际关系网
talk and expand my network.
鬼扯
Bullshit.
你是来找我抱怨雷·阿布鲁佐的
You invited me out to bitch about Ray Abruzzo.
你就这么懂我啊
You can read me that well, huh?
是啊
Yep.
是啊 老兄
Yeah, man.
这么些年来 我也替他背了不少黑锅了
I've taken a lot of his bullshit over the years.
真不少了
And I mean I've taken a lot.
可他们把我的位子给了他
But once they gave him my spot on dirty side
我说不好 兄弟
I don't know, man.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你能想象如果是我们 会怎么样吗
Can you imagine if it was either of us?
靠
Shit.
现在他回来 开始自己发号施令了
And now that he's back he's calling his own shots.
没错 警长说我不能碰
Yeah. The captain says I have to pull back
小萨尔谋杀案的唯一嫌犯
on the only suspect Ihave from this Lil Sal murder
就为了给弗劳利案让路
to make way for this Frawley case.
你要我的意见吗
You want my advice?
对这事儿
There's not a damn thing
你根本无能为力
you can do about it.
告诉我 你到底是怎么想的
Well, tell me how you really feel.
他是不会改变的
He's never gonna change.
但这就是好消息
But that's the good news.
他是不会改变的
He's never gonna change.
他会一次又一次地搞砸
He's gonna mess up again and again.
但你呢
But you?
是你把弗兰基·奎瓦斯压在了监狱里
You're the guy who's keeping Frankie Cuevas in prison.
这就是你的中奖彩票
That's your winning ticket.
好了 各位 从今天起
AlI right, guys, starting today,
这就是我们的新目标 肖恩和欧文·弗劳利
these are our new targets, Shane and Owen Frawley.
你们都认识肖恩的
Now, you guys know Shane.
他是南波士顿的老派黑帮恶棍 年纪不小了
He's an old- school mob prick from Southie post- Whitey era
我们小欧文在伍斯特打小联盟3A棒球
Little Owen here played Triple A ball in Worcester.
因为卖兴奋剂和袭击队友
He got dropped from the team for selling PEDs
被队里开除了
and assaulting a teammate.
这小鬼烂得很
Kid sucks.
好了 行动计划
So, uh, you got your operational plans
在你们面前了
in front of you.
所有新目标都在里头了
You have all the new targets in there,
但请各位特别注意一下
but I want you to take a special look
我们的老朋友奥西托
at our old friend Osito.
我们认为他一直在给弗劳利叔侄供货
We believe he has been supplying the Frawleys.
至少在我们除掉纽约的毒贩之前是这样的
Or at least he was until we took out New York.
所以在他们忙着找货的时候
So in this scramble for product,
我们要利用好现在的混乱
we want to capitalize on the chaos.
任务都已经派下去了 哦对 还有一件事
You guys got your assignments. Oh, one more thing.
这是莎拉·基根
This is Sarah Keegan.
她是本次行动的新卧底
She's our new undercover on this operation.
没有我的同意 都不许和她有联系
No one communicates with her unless I say so.
在外注意安全 各位 去抓坏人了
Be safe out there, guys. Let's go get them.
杰基 我想带莎拉出去了解一下
Jackie, I want to take Sarah out to get
大致情况 你跟我们一起
the lay of the land. I want you with us.
杰基 这是莎拉 莎拉这是杰基
So Jackie, Sarah. Sarah, Jackie.
-你好  -嗨
What's up? - Hi.
好极了 我们走
Great. Let's go.
到时候了呢 探员
Guess what time it is, Agent?
这才过去一天吧
I mean, it's only been, like, a day.
所以这才叫随机抽检
That's why they call it random.
没关系 我们等你
Hey, don't worry about it. We'll wait.
她骂人用俄语
♪ Her curse words In Russian ♪
以前你会聊起你喜欢的人
♪ You used to share Who you liked ♪
逃离警察
♪ Getting away from the cops ♪
你肯定都烦这些事儿了吧
This has to be getting old for you.
能请你坐到位置上去吗
Can you take a seat at your desk?
为什么 怎么了
Why? What's wrong?
请你去坐下
Just take a seat, please.
这车好 我肯定会买
Great car. Definitely one I'd go for.
好
Okay.
嗨 蠢货
What up, fool?
那小鬼没来啊
Boy didn't show.
我带你去试驾
I'd love to take you for a test drive.
等我拿下卡宴的钥匙
Let me grab the keys to the Cayenne.
这把手跟顶级自行车似的 老兄
Handles like a fucking Masi, bro.
牛逼
God damn.
德国制造
German engineering. -
都他妈给我让开
Go the fuck out of the way!
所以出什么事了 老兄
So what happened, bro, huh?
遇到点小挫折
Had a minor setback.
混蛋
Assholel
你他妈不如来服侍我的屌
How about you sit back on my fucking dick?
让开啊 傻逼
Move out of the way, you snatch.
你应该知道吧 要是你没货
You know, if you don't got product,
那你就是个二手车贩子而已
you're just a used car salesman.
我可以弄到货
I can get product.
但你他妈得让开点
I just need you to step the fuck off
给我点时间搞定我的生意
and give me a minute to get my business sorted out.
我只是想说
Alls I'm saying is,
你自己留了个洞出来 就怪不得别人填上了
leave a hole, it's gonna get filled.
生命的循环罢了
Circle of life.
肯定没事的
I'm sure it's all good.
我想也是
Yeah. I'm sure.
杰基 能说两句吗
Jackie, can we talk to you for a second?
知道为什么叫你来吗
Do you know why you're here?
不知道
No idea.
你尿检大麻阳性
You tested positive for marijuana.
等等 什么 我 我不抽大麻的啊
Wait, what? I don't- - I don't smoke weed.
-所以是尿检出错了  -是啊
So the test was wrong? - Yes. Yes.
你在受雇于马萨诸塞州州警期间
Did you or did you not use marijuana while employed
有没有使用过大麻
by the Massachusetts State Police?
我没有 那检测有问题
I did not. That test is fucked.
而且我不是州警的人
And I don't work for State Police.
-我是联邦探员  -到此为止了
I'm a federal agent. - That's it.
实验结束了
This experiment is over.
现在你是你们机构的麻烦了
You're your agency's problem now.
这什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是你不再是这个组的一员了
It means you're off the unit.
搞什么 就为了大麻吗 这他妈不是合法的吗
What the fuck? Over weed, which is fucking legal?
-杰基  -你知道的吧 要不是我
- Jackie- - - You know Frankie Cuevas
现在弗兰基·奎瓦斯根本不会在坐牢
wouldn't be in prison right now if it wasn't for me?
那你知道没有你 现在谁会在牢里吗 夏梅恩·格拉萨
And you know who would be? Charmaine Grasa.
所以这就是你让两个女的
So that's what you get for putting two females
在一线搭档的结果是吧 警监
in the field together, huh, Lieutenant?
够了
That's enough.
请你立刻交出警徽和枪
You'll turn over your gun and badge now.
操你妈
Fuck this, man.
-就现在  -咱们
Now! - Let's talk
-晚点再聊  -该死的
- about this later. - God damn it.
-搞什么 杰基  -什么搞什么
- What the hell, Jackie? - What the hell what?
-我什么都没做  -你做了
- I didn't do anything. - Yeah, actually, you did.
-你抽了大麻  -我跟你说了我没有
- You smoked some weed. - I told you I didn't.
你还跑进去冲着警监发火
And you went in there and you got an attitude with the LT?
还跟他说脏话
You drop some F- bombs on him?
对 因为他是个傻逼
Yeah, cause he's a dick.
是啊 他是那个自从夏梅恩的事情之后
Yeah, he's the dick who wanted to get rid of you
就想除掉你的傻逼
since the Charmaine thing.
我他妈一直在挺你
And I fucking went to bat for you.
我让你重回一线了
I got you off desk duty.
现在我成蠢货了
I look like the fucking asshole now.
那也去你妈的
Yeah, well, fuck you very much too.
杰基 杰基
Jackie. Jackiel
如果真的只是大麻 那还有转圜余地
If it really is just weed, we got wiggle room here.
你得学会怎么跟警监打交道
Now, you gotta learn how to play the LT.
刚才那样是铁定不行的
And that was not it.
你还要不要我帮你跟他说说
So you want me to talk to him for you?
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah, really.
你先回家 冷静一下
So why don't you just go home and cool off.
好 行
Yeah, okay.
好 但听着
Okay. But hey.
你得交出枪和警徽
I'm gonna need your gun and badge.
-你他妈认真的吗  -拜托
Are you fucking serious? - Please.
别让事情更难做
Do not make this any harder than it already is.
不 杰基
No- - Jackie.
杰基 对不起
Jackie, I'm sorry.
是我老公给我吃了软糖 我真的不知道
My husband gave me gummy bears. I had no idea.
操
Fuck.
可以吗
You got it?
-嗨  -好了 过来吧
Hi. Right, come here.
扯到我耳环了
Ohh. Got my earring.
-松手  -小心点
Oh, let go. Okay, okay. Careful.
小弗兰基会乖乖的
Frankie Jr. is gonna be a good boy
帮忙照顾妹妹的
and help take care of his sister.
-对吧 小伙子  -对 妈妈
Right, bud? - Yes, Mommy
我也不是很久没照顾过宝宝了
Hasn't been that long since I took care of a baby.
昨天才干过
I just watched them yesterday.
对吧
Right?
好了 爱你
AII right, love you.
好了 宝贝 我爱你
AII right, baby, I love you.
好 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
顺便问一句 你这连着两天盛装打扮的
By the way, where you going all dressed up
去哪儿啊
two days in a row?
你不用担心 妈 这周忙
Don't worry about it, Ma. Crazy week.
行吧
Oh, okay.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
来吧 小伙子 我们进去
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
早 女士
Mornin", ma'am.
我不知道你记不记得我
I don't know if you remember me- -
我记得你
I remember you.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
你来干什么
So what're you here for?
我来找夏梅恩
I'm looking for Charmaine.
挺久没她消息了
Haven't heard from her in a while.
如果你是问她有没有被抓
If you're asking if she's locked up,
那就没有
then the answer is no.
但如果你是在问她有没有跟警方合作
But if you're asking if she's cooperating,
那你应该是知道的
you should know better.
我不是想问这个
That's not what I'm asking
纽约的生意 现在出大问题了
The business in New York, it's a real problem for me.
我得找到新货源 才能继续把生意做下去
I need to find a new source to keep things up and running.
那我还得修热水器呢
And I need my water heater fixed,
你看我抱怨了吗
but you don't see me complaining.
我会派人过来的
I'lI send one of my guys over.
你还需要什么
What else you need?
格拉萨家一直都很照顾我
The Grasas have always looked after me.
回报是我应该做的
Least I could do is pay that back.
我们依赖纽约那边很久了
We've been leaning on New York for a long while.
我们也很难做
We struggling too.
我知道韦恩肯定会想出办法来
I know Wayne's gonna work something out,
但这需要时间
but it's gonna take some time.
我跟你说实话吧
I ain't gonna lie to you.
我是真没时间了
Time is something that I don't have much of.
那我也帮不了你了
Well then, I guess there's nothing more I can do for you.
要打包带走吗
You want a plate to go?
我不小心听到了 你说你一直在挺杰基
I, uh, overheard you going to bat for Jackie.
你们关系很好吗
Are you guys close?
你知道我们这是在干什么吗
What you think it is we're doing out here?
-卧底行动  -没错
An undercover operation. Exactly.
所以你能不能专心在这上面
So why don't you stay focused on that?
-明白 长官  -我不是
- Yes, sir. - Im not here
来跟你交朋友的 也不是
to be your friend, I'm not here
来跟你闲扯淡的
to chitchat with you.
我是来确保你的安全的
I'm here to make sure you stay safe.
-明白了吗  -明白
You got it? - Got it.
你要知道 买毒品真没那么难
You know, it's really not that hard to buy drugs.
马戏团里的猴子都能做到
A circus monkey could do it.
你要毒品 他们也想给你
You want something, and they wanna give it to you.
所以你做自己就行 但这不一样
So just be yourself, but different.
是 做我自己
Yes. Be myself.
也是马戏团的猴子
But also a circus monkey.
还有一件事
One more thing.
你长得漂亮 所以男人会想
You're cute, so guys are gonna wanna
免费给你东西 但你不能要
give you stuff for free, but you can't take it.
你得付钱 否则会毁了
You gotta pay for it, or else it's gonna mess up
-证据链的  -好
- the chain of evidence. - Mm- hmm.
喂 你叫什么
Yo, what's your name?
-凯拉·沃克  -不 不是的
- Kayla Walker. - No, it's not.
不是的 你叫莎拉
It's not. It's Sarah.
不要编假的名字
You don't give yourself a fake first name
因为会忘
'cause you forget it.
你这第一天就要完蛋
You're gonna fuck up day one.
做你自己
Be yourself.
要保持一致 但又不一样
I want you to be the same, but different.
行吧 我是莎拉·沃克
Fine. I'm Sarah Walker.
你哪里人 莎拉·沃克
Where you from, Sarah Walker?
斯普林菲尔德
Springfield.
但我刚从佛罗里达州立大学毕业
But, uh, I just graduated from Florida State,
美国排名第二的爱玩学校
number two party school in America.
那你来鳕鱼角干什么
What you doing on the Cape, then?
就是来好好享受夏天的
Oh, I'm just here for the summer, vibin',
住在我朋友父母家里
staying at a friend's parents' place.
-你工作了吗  -现在没有
You working? - Not right now.
我领残疾津贴的
I'm on disability.
你看着没什么问题啊
You look good to me.
这里头有问题
Not in here.
好 行
AlI right. All right.
靠
Shit.
该死的
God damn it.
马萨诸塞州 鳕鱼角
Massachusetts. Cape Cod.
菲奥娜 克里斯托 米兰达
Fiona. Crystal. Miranda.
好了 维罗妮卡 找到你了
AlI right, Veronica. Got you.
- 5- 5- 0- 1- 6- 4.
喂
Hello?
喂 搞什么
- Hello? What the fuck?
搞什么
What the fuck?
维罗妮卡 艾冯
我们想和你一起玩
靠
Oh, shit.
艾玛
Emma.
艾玛 艾玛 艾玛
Emma, Emma, Emma.
你的电话已被转到
Your call has been forwarded
自动语音留言系统
to an automatic voice message system.
嗨 艾玛
- Hi, Emma.
我想好好玩玩 给我回电话
I'm looking to party. Call me back.
随时可以见 哪里都可以
I can meet you any time, anywhere.
是我 埃德
It's Ed!
操
Fuck.
操 操
Fuck, fuck.
等我一下
Uh, give me a sec.
等一下 等一下
Uh, one second, one second.
嗨 你好啊
Hey, what's up?
你怎么来了
What're you doing here?
琳达给你的香蕉面包
Banana bread from Linda.
她跟你问好呢
She says hi. -
我接到了雷的电话
I got a call from Ray.
他说你尿检没过
Said you failed your drug test.
对 不是 就是个误会
Yeah. No, it's just a it's a misunderstanding.
我是干净的 一直都是
I'm clean. I've been clean.
不 你不是
No, you haven't.
至少从圣诞开始 你就在疯玩了
You've been partying since at least Christmas.
你怎么知道的
How the hell would you know? Huh?
因为你已经躲了我那么久了
Because that's how long you've been avoiding me.
操
Fuck.
对不起
I'm sorry. JB. R
就是 你知道的
It's just...you know.
我被踢出组了
I'm off the unit.
雷说他会想办法挽救 但
Ray says he's gonna try to fix it, but
我他妈就跟时间错位了一样
It's like I'm in a fucking time warp.
所以你就准备待在这儿自怨自艾吗
So you just gonna sit around feeling sorry for yourself?
还是准备爬起来
Or are you gonna get up off your ass
去参加互助会
and go to a fucking meeting?
我不会去互助会的
I'm not going to a fucking meeting.
-事儿太多了  -对
- I got too much going on. - Right.
你去不了互助会
You can't go to a meeting.
你忙着被炒鱿鱼呢
You're so busy getting yourself fired.
老天 行吧 我可以去互助会
Jesus. Okay, I can go to a meeting.
我只是不想去
Ijust don't want to.
我宁愿拿个叉子捅自己眼珠子
I'd rather stick a fork in my eye.
出什么事了
What happened?
你以前一直都去的 你可喜欢互助会了
You used to go all the time. You loved those meetings.
以前我觉得自己是可以改变的
Well, I used to think that I could change.
但现在我连试都不想试了 老兄
But now I don't even wanna try, man.
我没准备好面对那一切
I'm just not ready for all that.
那或许你没必要准备好呢
Well, maybe you don't have to be ready.
我不想去想戒毒的事儿 埃德
I don't want to think about my sobriety, Ed.
我的破事儿太多了 真的太多了
I got too much shit going on. I really do.
真的是很大的破事儿
I got, like, some major shit going on.
-哪种破事儿  -操
- What kind of shit? - Fuck.
说来话长
It's too long to explain.
有人需要帮助
Somebody needs help.
而我觉得 自己得去帮忙
And- and I feel like I'm the one who needs to help them.
来吧
Come on.
就去一次互助会
Just one meeting.
我开车送你
I'll be your chauffeur.
我开的凯迪拉克
I brought the Caddy.
-我喜欢那辆  -我知道
- I do like the Caddy. - I know.
走吧
Come on.
抱歉 我得接这个电话
I'm sorry. I gotta take this.
嗨 嗨
Hell- - uh, hello?
你给我留言了吗
You left me a message?
对 嗨 艾玛
Yeah, hi, Emma.
我能见你一面吗
I was wondering if I could see you.
在哪儿能见
Where could we meet?
我在福尔布鲁克
I'm in Fall Brook.
今晚我和一些姐妹要去鳕鱼角
Me and some of the girls are headed to the Cape tonight.
哈威奇28号路上的沙棘
We'll be at the Seaberry on 28 in Harwich.
可以吗
That work for you?
维罗妮卡会跟你一起吗
Is Veronica gonna be with you?
维罗妮卡
Veronica's, um...
今天没空
she's not available.
你要别人吗
Do you want someone else?
不 那就你好了
No. Just you then.
行 8点
Okay, eight o'clock.
我到了之后给你发房间号
I'll text you a room number when I get there.
200块 现金或者礼品卡
It'll be $200. Cash or a Visa gift card.
-好 行  -可以
Okay. Okay. - Sweet.
来了点事儿
So something just came up.
我得出门了
I gotta hit the road soon.
-好  -抱歉
Right. - I'm sorry.
-下次可以吗  -行
Maybe we can raincheck? - Oh, sure.
今晚还去互助会吗
Still gonna hit that meeting tonight?
可以啊 或者明天
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Or tomorrow.
我不知道你到底要找什么
I just don't know what you're looking for
但希望你能找到吧
from this thing, but I hope you fucking find it.
记得给我打电话 杰基
Give me a call sometime, Jack.
拜托 就快好了
Come on, we're almost there.
老天
Ow, Jesus.
压到我手指了
Ow, it's pinching my finger.
看上去你们有点忙不过来啊
Looks like you got your hands full.
我来帮你们
Let me help you out.
我的天
Oh, my God.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
没事 我是瑞秋
No problem. I'm Rachel.
我是街那头约翰逊家的保姆
I nanny for the Johnsons down the street.
哦对 约翰逊家
Oh, right. The Johnsons.
我在找额外的工作
I'm looking for more hours.
所以如果有需要的话 随时找我
So, uh, let me know if you ever need some help.
虽然你已经做得很好了 这位妈妈
Even though you're obviously doing great, Mom.
我不是他们妈
I'm not their mother.
但你有没有名片之类的
But, uh do you have, like, a- like, a card?
-或者能留个号码吗  -可以啊
Or can I get your number? Yeah.
太好了
Okay, great.
你阴唇都出来了
Your labia was sticking out.
你知道规矩的
You know the rules.
后台 自己拿胶带
Backstage. Grab some tape.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这肯定不对
No, that can't be right.
我订了两箱 不是四箱
I ordered two cases, not four.
-行  -蕾妮 你能不能去后面办公室
- Okay. - Renee, can you run
帮我把上个月的订单拿来
to the back office and get me last month's order?
办公室吗
The office?
对 你还记得我们把订单
Yeah. You remember where we keep
都放哪里的吧
the order slips, right?
操
Fuck!
你找到了吗
You find it?
找到了
Yeah.
这里看着不一样了
It looks different in here.
他们重新刷过漆
They painted,
把地板换了 全都改掉了
ripped out the floor, everything.
不得不换
I mean, they had to.
毕竟之前到处都是体液 是吧
There was, like, bodily fluids in here, you know?
是我知道
Oh, yeah. No I know.
但这
But this.
这大漂亮了
this is beautiful.
桑蒂勒警官 我是州警库珀
Sergeant Saintille? Trooper Cooper.
怎么了
What's up?
我带来了你们的嫌犯
I brought in your person of interest.
你说谁
Who we talking about?
牙买加那个尚尼斯·拜利
Chanice Bailly. From Jamaica.
库珀警官 好兄弟
Trooper Cooper, my man.
-她人呢  -审讯室里 长官
- Where is she? - Interrogation room, sir.
对不起 我一般不开这么快的
I'm sorry. I usually don't drive so fast.
我上班要迟到了 他们扣我们工资
I was late to me shift, and they dock our pay.
-我  -你叫什么名字
And, I- - What's your name?
尚尼斯·拜利
Chanice Bailly.
是这么拼的吗
B- A- I- L- L- Y?
小姐 你知道你和一个正因一起谋杀而被通缉的女人
Ma'am, do you realize you have the exact same name
同名同姓吗
as a woman wanted in questioning for a murder?
不 我什么都不知道
No, I don't know nothin' about that.
听着 我会付罚款的 我发誓
Look, I will pay for the ticket, I swear.
好 好 行
Okay. Okay. All right.
咱们重新开始
Let's start again.
我是艾伦·桑蒂勒警探 我知道你很害怕
I'm Detective Alan Saintille. I know you're scared.
但你不帮我 我就帮不了你
But I can't help you unless you help me.
我觉得你不是尚尼斯·拜利
Now, I do not think you are Chanice Bailly.
你也不想做她
And I don't think you wanna be.
我买了假身份过来打工
I got fake papers to come here and work.
这是他给我的名字
And that's the name he gave me.
谁
Who?
移民律师 格林先生
The immigration lawyer. Mr. Green.
所有人都找他弄文书
Everybody goes to him for papers.
他要价很高 但我也没得选
He costs too much. But what choice do I have?
我在找的是这个人 你认识她吗
This is who I'm looking for. You know her?
不 我不认识
No, sir, I don't.
来 帮我个忙
Here, do me a favor.
写下那个律师的信息
Write down that lawyer's information.
放她走
Let her go.
帮我盯着点其他的尚尼斯·拜利
And keep an eye out for more Chanice Baillys.
明白吗
You got it?
好
Okay.
这里以前都是奎瓦斯的地盘
This all used to be Cuevas territory.
看来有新主人了
Looks like it's under new management.
你看看
Check it out. -
我看着像目标
Looks like a target to me.
我们只用做过标记的现钞
Now we only use marked bills
它能在法庭上救命
'cause it saves our ass in court.
但现在我们不用担心这些
But we don't have to worry about that
因为你不负责抓人
because you're not making an arrest.
融入进去就行
Just here to ingratiate yourself.
好吗 你现在过去
AlI right? You're gonna go in.
买点氧可酮 简单点
You're gonna buy a few Oxys. Keep it simple.
你不是塞尔皮科 好吗
You're not Serpico, okay?
不用管 就
Uh, never mind. Just
我给你打电话 别挂
I'ma call you. Keep your line open.
我会全程听着的
I'll be listening the whole time.
可以吗
You all right? -
嗨
What up?
你好
Hello?
你知道哪儿能买到氧可酮吗
You know where Icould score some Oxys?
你谁啊
Who are you?
从来没见过你
Never seen you around before.
我刚来的 来过夏天的
Well, Ijust got here. Im down for the summer.
听着 老兄 我疼得很
Look, dude, Im hurtin.
你到底能不能帮我
Can you help me out or what?
你要什么
What do you want?
我不知道这儿的价格
Mm, I don't know the prices here.
一百块能买到什么
You know, what can I get for $100?
能买四片80毫克的
That'll get you four OC80s.
但得去我车上
But we gotta run to my car.
不行
No.
不 不要上车
No, no. Don't get in the car.
-行  -好
Cool- AlI right.
蠢货 蠢货 蠢货
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
蠢货
Stupid.
把钱给我
Give me the money.
全拿出来
AII of it.
-还有钱包手机  -你抢劫我吗
Wallet and phone, too. - You're robbing me?
操 操
Aw, fuck. Fuck! -
-你真他妈离谱  -那我们这破地方
Man, that's really fucked up. That's how it goes
就是这样的 婊子
in motherfuckin' Hightown, bitch.
行吧
Okay. Fine.
老天
Jesus.
操
Ahh! Fuck!
老天
God.
操 操 真他妈疼
Fuck, fuck! Ah, shit, it hurtsl
靠 真他妈疼
Oh, shit. Shit, that hurts.
立刻趴地上
Hey, get on the fucking ground right now.
给我下车 趴地上
Get out of the fucking car. Get on the fucking ground.
立刻趴地上
Get on the fucking ground right now.
州警
State police.
你 也给我趴下
You, stay on the fucking ground.
你也被捕了 听到没
You're under arrest, too. You hear me?
抱歉 蕾妮
Hey, sorry, Renee.
你等一下 塔菲
Yeah, you wanna hold back, Taffy?
你们俩干什么呢
Hey. What were you two doing?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得你在本来该去外头赚钱的时候
I think that you were blowing lines in here
在这里嗑药
when you're supposed to be making money out there.
但我把可卡因卖给他了
Except I sold him the coke.
所以我在这里也是在赚钱
So I'm making money in here, too.
我不管你到底干什么
I don't give a shit what you do
除非你在我的俱乐部里卖可卡因
unless you're selling coke in my club.
那我就在乎了
Then I give a shit.
你在这儿赚的每一分钱 俱乐部都要分一块
Every dime you make in here the club gets a piece of.
如果你是要回扣 直接说不就完了
If you're asking for a kickback, just say so.
我不是要你那垃圾小苏打
Yeah, I'm not asking for a kickback
卖出来钱的回扣 好吗
on your skeezy little lines of baking soda, okay?
你怎么这么讨人厌
Why you being a bitch?
你要是有更好的货卖
If you have better coke to sell,
那带我一个啊
sign me up.
嗨 兄弟
What up, brother?
之后手头可能要紧了
Might be some lean times soon.
我来盘一下你们手里的货
Came to check how far you think you can stretch
还够挺多久的
what you got on hand.
可能一两天吧
Guess, maybe a day or two.
我没让你猜 我让你盘一下
I didn't ask you to guess. I asked you to check.
还有什么事儿
So what else is up? -
没什么
Chillin'. -
就一天的货了 你没想着给我个电话吗
One day of product? You ain't think to call me?
你不担心没货吗
You ain't worried about runnin'out?
没有 就
Nah, just
听说你事儿比较多
heard you had a lot going on.
这是你听说的吗
That's- that's what you heard hmm?
或者你觉得 有别的途径可以补货
Or maybe you think the re- up is coming from somewhere else.
喂 老奥 回来
yo, O, man, come back
我说什么了
What I say?
好了
Got it Ohl
上路
On the rail.
我们得聊聊
You and me need to talk.
行 进来吧
Sure. Come on in.
要冰激凌吗
You want a ice cream?
不要啊
No?
这话我就说一次
I'ma say this shit one time.
你别插手 不然 会有后果的
You stand down or there's gonna be consequences.
这话够狠的啊
Well, that's some strong words.
你跟欧文准备给鳕鱼角供货
Thought you and Owen was gonna start supplying the Cape,
在我的地盘 找我的人
go to my boys on my blocks,
开始抢我的生意
and start filling my orders.
但事情没那么容易
But it's not gonna go that way.
如果你继续这么干
And if you keep this shit up,
我保证 你肯定不会喜欢接下来的事的
I promise you won't like what happens next.
老奥 别紧张
O, relax.
你可别心脏病发了
I don't need you catching a heart attack.
没必要这么激动
There's no need to get worked up.
别油嘴滑舌的了 让他给我滚远点
Fuck that slick shit. Tell him to back the fuck off.
我可能是老了 但你这么跑来
I may be an old dog, but you come in here,
来威胁我
you start tossing threats around,
那你要知道 老办法我可都记着呢
you should know I remember all the old tricks.
我不想诉诸暴力
I don't want violence.
但如果你跟我对上 那一定是我赢
But if it's me against you, it's gonna be me
相信我
Believe that.
远离我的地盘 我的人
Back the fuck off my blocks and my boys
不然就开战
or there's gonna be war.
你还太年轻 没资格提开战 小伙子
You're awfully young to speak about war, son.
瞧 是阿尔伯特·菲茨杰拉德
Hey, hey, hey. It's Albert Fitzgerald.
道上的人叫你什么
So, what do they call you on the street?
-菲茨  -好 菲茨
Fitzy Okay, Fitzy.
你未按时出庭 身上背着逮捕令
You got an open warrant for failure to appear in court.
现在你还被抓到用致命性武器
And now we got you for assaulting a police officer
袭击警官
with a deadly weapon.
基根警官 认识吧
You know Trooper Keegan, right?
嗨 菲茨
Hey, Fitzy.
操
Fuck.
老兄 你要什么就直说
Yo, man, just tell me what you want.
-你着急走吗  -不
You in a hurry? - Nah.
我知道这破事儿怎么回事
I just know how this shit works.
你们要是没有所图 那我现在应该在牢房里
If you didn't want nothing, I'd be in a cell.
你了解肖恩·弗劳利吗
What do you know about Shane Frawley?
我他妈可太了解肖恩·弗劳利了
I know fuck all about Shane Frawley.
那他侄子欧文呢
What about his nephew Owen?
老兄 我不跟他们打交道
Man, I don't deal with them.
你在弗劳利的地盘上卖货
Cause you're dealing in Frawley land,
不跟他们打交道 你他妈跟谁打交道呢
so if you don't deal with them, who the fuck do you deal with?
操你妈
Fuck you.
这对我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
我告诉你这有什么好处
I'll tell you what's in it for you.
喜欢阳光吗
You like sunshine?
不配合 就等着过六年不见天日的日子吧
Cause you ain't gonna see it for six fucking years, kid.
别扯皮了 赶紧给我吐干净
Quit jerking me off and tell me what I want to hear.
或许今晚你还有机会睡自己的床
Maybe I let you sleep in your own bed tonight.
有个叫雷德的
Some dude named Red.
他是欧文的司机 毒品是他给我的
He's Owen's driver. He gives me the drugs.
我负责卖货
I sell them.
听到了吗
You hear that?
我们菲茨会把你介绍给他好兄弟雷德的
Fitzy here is gonna introduce you to his boy Red.
嗨 别跑啊
Hi. Hey, don't run
怎么样
How was it?
他乖得很
He was a perfect angel.
她拉了三次
She had three poopy diapers.
好 那你明天还有空吗
Okay, so are you still good for tomorrow?
我没空约了做头发
Actually, no. I have a hair appointment.
什么 那我该怎么办
What? What am I supposed to do?
别紧张 我都搞定了
Relax. I got it covered.
我今天遇到个很可爱的保姆
I met this sweet nanny lady today.
-谁  -她叫瑞秋
- Who? - Her name's Rachel.
人都有红十字认证的
She's, like, Red Cross certified and everything.
瑞秋 好
Rachel, okay.
这样 我现在就把她号码发给你
Look, I'll- I'lI text you her number right now.
好极了 我这就去让那个彻头彻尾的陌生人
Oh, yeah, great. Ill just have a total stranger
帮我照顾孩子 妈
watch my kids, Mom.
你检查过她的履历了吗
Did you even check her references?
她是约翰逊家的保姆
She works for the Johnsons.
约翰逊家 好
The Johnsons. Okay.
不用谢
You're welcome.
嗨 瑞秋
Hi, Rachel?
我是蕾妮 我妈把你的号码给我了
My name is Renee. I got your number from my mom.
对 抱歉这么临时
Yeah, uh, I'm sorry about the last minute call.
但我想问问
But, um, I was just wondering
明早或许我们能见一面吗
if maybe we could meet tomorrow morning?
就 如果感觉合得来的话
And, you know, if things feel right,
或许明天你能帮我照顾下孩子吗
maybe you could babysit the rest of the day?
那太棒了
Oh, that's amazing.
好 行 完美
Yes. Okay, perfect.
谢谢你 太感谢了 好 到时候见
Thank you. Thank you so much. Okay, I'll see you then.
241.
240.
嗨 你好啊
Well, hello.
我是来找艾玛的
Yeah. Uh, I'm here for Emma.
好 你带钱来了吗
All right. You got some money?
带了 我给她
Yeah. I'll give it to her.
不 钱给我 我来给她
No, you give it to me. I'll give it to her.
行吧
Fine.
进来吧 小姑娘
AlI right. Come on in, girlie.
艾玛人呢
Where's Emma?
她还在别人那里收尾呢
She's, uh, you know, finishing up with somebody.
怎么 不喜欢我们陪吗
What, you don't like the company?
没事
- No, it's fine.
你不错
You're fine.
你可太不错了
You are fuckin' fine.
提问 你是条子吗
Question. You a cop?
什么 不是
What? No.
不是
No.
搜她身
Strip search her.
确保她没骗人
Let's make sure she ain't lying.
不不不 我
No. No, no, I'm- I'm- -
-开玩笑的  -老天
Fucking kidding you. - Jeez.
操
Fuck.
坐下吧
Fucking sit down.
放松啊 服了
Relax. God damn.
来一口吗 给她来一口 老兄
Hey, you want a hit? Give her a fucking hit, man.
不用了
I'm good. I'm fine.
给我吧
Give me.
所以
So, uh
你们跟另一个姑娘也是一起的吗 那个维罗妮卡
You work with that other girl, too? Veronica?
不 我不认识什么维罗妮卡
No, I don't know any fucking Veronicas.
没事 我只是好奇
It's all good. I was just curious.
你问那什么维罗妮卡干什么
Why you asking about some bitch named Veronica?
你不喜欢现在
You don't like the fucking bitch
-约的这个婊子吗  -不不不
you got a date with or what? - No. No, no, no.
不是 就是
It's not that. She just- -
我之前跟她搞上过
she's just some chick that I hooked up with.
我以为你们认识她
I thought, uh, you knew her is all.
那我不认识
Well, I don't.
行吧
All right.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
不 操
No, no. Fuck no.
不不不不不
Fuck. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
操 你得赶紧滚
Shit, you gotta get the fuck out.
-什么  -我叫你
- I said you gotta
- 赶紧滚  -老天 行吧
- get the fuck out of here! - Jesus! Okay, fine.
那钱还我啊
Just give me my money, man.
不 你他妈赶紧给我滚
- No, you gotta get the fuck
你这大嘴巴
out of here, you big mouth- -
-行 那我钱呢  -走啊
Okay. My fucking money! Go.
给我滚 臭婊子
I said get the fuck out, bitch!
斯韦齐 什么情况
Swayzee, what is happening?
艾玛 我得跟你聊聊 我得
Emma, I need to talk to you. I need to talk- -
艾玛 给我滚回去
Emma, get back in the fucking room.
-赶紧的  -我只是想跟她聊聊
Right fucking now. - I just need to talk to her.
让我跟她聊聊
Let me talk to her.
让我
Just lemme- -
行吧 操
Okay, fine. Shit. Fuck.
操 行吧 我这就走
Fuck, fine. Fine. Fine. I'm going. I'm going.
-嗨  -喂 彼得
Hello. - Yo, Petey.
是我可爱的奶油山核桃小宝贝吗
Oh, is this my sweet, little, butter- pecan- Rican?
你认得那个叫斯韦齐的吗 维罗妮卡的皮条客
You know this guy Swayzee? Veronica's pimp?
斯韦齐 认识啊
Swayzee? Yeah, I know him.
他就是个人渣
He's a fucking piece of shit.
而且他跟一些惹不得的人有关系
And he's hooked up with very serious motherfuckers.
我们刚见了一面 起了点争执
Well, we just met. Got a bit gnarly.
我也没资格跟你说该做什么
Well, far be it from me to tell you what to do.
但我建议你还是离他远一点
But I would advise you to stay the fuck away from him.
行吧
Yeah, okay.
老大
- Boss?
我 去找了那个移民律师
So I, uh, took a run at the immigration lawyer.
发现这傻逼在重复利用护照
Turns out this fucking mope was recycling visas
来避开限额规定 现在要面对联邦起诉了
to dodge the quota cap. He's facing federal charges.
所以 他把清洁工的真实姓名给我们了
So he gave us the real names of our cleaning ladies.
复杂起来了啊
Oh, the plot thickens.
这是安吉拉·坎贝尔 化名尚尼斯
Meet Angela Campbell, AKA Chanice,
这是洛林·戈登 化名卡米娜
and Lorraine Gordon, AKA Carmina.
但是两个月前洛林
Except Lorraine died in a car accident
死于一场车祸
two months ago.
所以现在就剩一个人了
So now we're down to one.
等牙买加政府找到她 就会交给我们了
But when Jamaican authorities find her, she's ours.
只花了六个月
Only took six months.
这事儿
Well, that's, uh
办得不错 警探
good policework, Sergeant.
多谢
Thanks.
我正准备出去
Hey, I was gonna head out.
辣椒喷雾的事儿
The thing with the pepper spray...
一定得写进报告里吗
do we have to put it in the report?
你是让我把它瞒下来吗
Are you asking me to omit it?
我
Well, I
这让我显得有点蠢
it kind of makes me look stupid.
那确实是蠢
It was stupid.
好吧
Okay.
你搞砸了
Yeah, you screwed up.
你让他看到了你身上那么多现金
You showed him all your cash.
你还上了他的车
You got in his vehicle.
然后你还在封闭空间里
Then you discharged pepper spray
用了辣椒喷雾 你指望我怎么做
in an enclosed space. What do you want me to do?
你说得对
You're right.
所以 你准备聊聊吗 还是
So, like, do you want to talk about it, or.
听着 我不知道你
Look, I don't know if you're just pulling
是不是单纯开我玩笑
my pigtails or whatever,
但或许你可以想个办法
but maybe you can figure out a way to train me
不用这么混蛋 也可以训练我的
without being a total dick.
顺带一提 我这第一天就带我们
And by the way, I got us into the Frawley organization
进到了弗劳利组织里
on day one.
谁这么晚给你打电话
Who's calling you this late?
你的网友吗
Is it one of your chat line friends?
你不用管 奶奶
Don't worry about it, Nana.
关门
Shut the door!
喂
Hello?
嗨 是我
Hey, it's me.
我的天 我做到了 成功了
Oh, my God, I did it. It worked.
我明天要去看孩子
I'm babysitting tomorrow.
你太棒了
You're amazing.
我想问 我们能不能 说点骚话
So I was thinking, can we, like, dirty talk?
我要你抚摸自己
I want you to touch yourself.
你也一样
I want you to do it too.
宝贝 我的鸡巴硬得不行
Oh, baby, my cock is so hard.
替我摸摸它
Touch it for me.
摸着呢
I am.
只为你
Just for you.
棒
Mm. Yeah.
太棒了 宝贝 给我弄出响儿来
Fuck yeah, baby. Make that fucking ass clap.
没错 就是这样 宝贝
Just like that. Fuck yeah, baby.
我的天 瞧瞧你多性感
Oh, my God. Look how fucking sexy you are.
来啊
Clap.
就这样 对着我的脸
Clap for me right on my face like that.
棒啊 瞧瞧这屁股
Fuck yeah. Look at that fucking ass.
继续 宝贝 继续啊
Yeah, make it clap, baby. Make that shit clap.
继续
Make it clap.
棒 宝贝 现在摸你自己奶头
Hell yeah, baby. Now touch your titties.
摸你自己奶头 没错
Touch your titties. Fuck yeah.
摸她奶头
Now touch her titty.
吸它们 没错 舔上去
Suck on'em. Fuck yeah. Lick that tit now.
给我舔上去
Fucking lick that shit.
-操  -好啊
Oh, fuck. - Oh, yeah.
我超爱
I love it.
舔上去 棒啊宝贝
Lick that shit, baby. Fuck yeah.
太棒了
Oh, fuck yeah.
老兄 你是在打飞机吗
Bro, are you jerking off?
是啊 喜欢看我
Yeah, you like watching me touch
摸自己的大鸡巴吗 宝贝
my big fucking cock, baby?
也没有
Not really.
都他妈给我闭嘴 继续跳
Why don't you shut the fuck up and keep dancing, huh?
跳啊
Fucking dance.
赶紧的
Go. Dance.
棒啊 宝贝
Ah, fuck yeah, baby.
你们真是太性感了
You girls are so fucking sexy.
我真他妈服了
Ah, for fuck's sake.
-喂  -把你鸡巴收起来
- Yo. - Put your cock away.
搞什么 肖恩叔
What the fuck, Uncle Shane?
恶心死了
Jesus. Disgusting.
抱歉 女士们 请你们出去
Excuse me, ladies. We're gonna need the room.
你来干什么
What you doing here?
你搞了点什么事儿 惊动到大块头了是吧
Oh, you riled the big man up something fierce, didn't you?
你惹到老虎了
You poked the beast.
非得现在聊这些吗
We gotta talk about that right now?
给我放清醒点
Get your shit together.
我们要开战了
We're going to war.
走啊
Move!
混蛋
Your asses.
来了
Coming.
我也希望我能肯定
♪I wish I was certain ♪
赶紧动起来
Gotta get moving.
天堂拉开帷幕
♪ Heaven pull back The curtain ♪
就在我面前
♪In front of my eyes ♪
我希望自己是个动物
♪I wish I was an animal ♪
那事情就简单很多
♪Then things would be Simpler ♪
因为思绪如同食人族
♪Cause thoughts are Like cannibals ♪
我是他们的囚徒
♪And I'm ♪ust their prisoner ♪
给我一个暗示
♪ Give me a sign ♪
让我下定决心
♪ To make up my mind ♪
因为疑心始终环绕着我
♪Cause doubt It does haunt me ♪
黑暗想要夺走我
♪And the darkness It wants me ♪
给我一个暗示
♪ Give me a sign ♪
因为有时候我是盲目的
♪Cause sometimes I'm blind ♪
这种黑暗无比诡异
♪And this blackness is Eerie ♪
要是我能看清就好了
♪ Oh, if I could see clearly ♪
雷 嗨
Ray. Hi.
你猜怎么着 我跟史密斯警监聊过了
Guess what? I talked to Lieutenant Smith.
你伤他很深
Now, you wound him up pretty good,
但我想了点办法
but I did some razzle dazzle
他同意让你去治疗
and he's willing to let you go to treatment.
什么治疗
Treatment?
对 是佛罗里达的一个地方
Yeah, yeah. It's a place down in Florida.
所有条子都是去那儿的
AlI the cops go there.
你去 就能回来
You go there, you're back on.
你来一下 我们谈清楚吧
Why don't you come in and we ll figure this out?
咱能晚点再说嘛
Yeah, well, can we talk about this later?
现在不太方便 我摸到大鱼了
It's not a good time right now. I'm onto something big.
嗨 艾玛 我知道你在家
Hello? Emma? I know you're home.
等下 搞什么 杰基
Hold on. What the fuck, Jackie?
什么叫晚点再说啊
What do you mean, talk about it later? Okay?
我现在是作为朋友在跟你说
I'm telling you this as a friend.
不管你在做什么 立刻停手
You stop whatever you're doing.
马上过来 不然我帮不了你
You come in here right now, or else I can't help you.
艾玛
Emma?
雷 我过会儿尽量过去
Ray, Ill try to stop by later,
-但我得挂了  -不不不
but I gotta go. No, no, no
-我不要听这些  -艾玛
- I don't want to hear that. - Emma?
杰基
Jackie.
艾玛
Emma. -
Emma.
醒醒 艾玛
Hey. Emma, hey.
拜托 艾玛 拜托 醒醒
Come on, Emma. Come on. Please, wake up.
醒醒 艾玛
Wake up, Emma.
操
Fuck.
艾玛
Emma.
艾玛 艾玛
Emma? Emma.
操 终于醒了
Fuck. There you are.
-嗨  -你他妈谁啊
Hey. - Who the fuck are you?
我是杰基 昨晚在汽车旅馆见过你
I'm Jackie, I met you at the motel last night.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事吧
You all right?
你给我用纳洛酮干什么
Why did you Narcan me, man?
-操  -你都要死了
Shit. - You were dying.
-我救了你  -鬼扯好吗
- I saved you. - Yeah, bullshit. All right?
你这是浪费了我辛辛苦苦挣来的毒品
Wasted some hard- earned fucking dope is what you did.
你他妈怎么进来的
How the fuck did you get in here?
你来干什么
What are you even doing here?
我把窗打破了 我会赔钱的
I had to break the window. I'll pay for it.
我是来问维罗妮卡的事情
I came here to ask you some questions about Veronica.
小维
V?
干什么 你他妈是条子啊
Why, are you a fucking cop?
不是
- No. -
你这样子可太像条子了
Sure as hell acting like one.
你他妈干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
很高兴认识你
Nice meeting you.
听着 让我 我就
Listen, just let me...I'll sit
操 让我留这儿行吗
Fuck. Just let me stay here, okay?
确保你安全
Just to be safe.
老姐 我他妈都不认识你好吗
Dude, I don't even fucking know you, okay?
我不在乎你在干什么
I don't care what you're doing.
我他妈根本不在乎你干什么
I don't give a shit what you do.
我只是 我不能接受你死我面前 好吗
I just- - I'm not cool with- with you dying on me, all right?
让我 以防万一
Let me just just to be safe.
行吧 随便吧
Fine. Yeah. Whatever.
拜托你这次别急着
Just don't get all trigger- happy
给我上纳洛酮了 行吗
with the Narcan this time, okay?
我累死了
I'm so tired.
没事的 你可以睡
It's okay. You can go to sleep.
没事的
It's fine. -
你要 你要拍拍我吗
you wanna- - you wanna rub my back?
行 好
Yeah, okay.
我真的好累
I'm so tired.
我一晚上都在做事一切
I was working all night, and everything's.
一切都这么操蛋
everything's so fucked up.
可怜的维罗妮卡
Poor Veronica.
我可怜的小维
My poor V.
太悲伤了
So sad.
真的太悲伤了
It was so sad.